tgw.com 2010-06-18

# Privacy Policy - www.tgw.com

|    
---  
Privacy Policy  
  
The Golf Warehouse is part of the Redcats USA family of companies, which currently includes 13 different brands. In order to help our customers better understand our policies regarding the collection and use of information as well as our general terms of use, Redcats USA has created one standardized Privacy Policy and Terms Of Use that will apply to all our brands. Accordingly, The Golf Warehouse has revised its Privacy Policy and Terms of Use as of May 21th, 2010.

**Privacy Statement**

Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to assist you in understanding the type of personal information we may collect from you, how such information may be used, the choices that are available to you concerning the use of your information and your ability to correct or modify the information you have provided us.

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may email us at [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com). We welcome your feedback and suggestions to help us improve our policies and practices. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to customers in the United States.

**Our Privacy Policy addresses the following**

  * Who is Redcats USA?
  * What Information Does Redcats USA Collect?
  * How Does Redcats USA Use the Information Collected?
  * What Information Is Shared And With Whom Is It Shared?
  * Does Redcats USA Use Third-Party Advertising?
  * How Can I Access and Correct Information Collected?
  * How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications From Redcats USA?
    * How to be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List
    * How to Unsubscribe from Email Marketing List
  * Are Redcats USA Division Credit Cards Available? 
  * Does Redcats USA Send Unsolicited Promotional Emails? 
  * How Does Redcats USA Safeguard the Information Collected? 
  * How Secure Is My Online Transaction? 
  * Does Redcats USA Use Cookies? 
  * Does Redcats USA Aggregate Information? 
  * What is Redcats USA's Policy with Respect to Data Collection from Children? 
  * Whom Do I Contact If I Have Additional Questions or Concerns About This Policy? 
  * Links to Other Websites
  * Policy Changes
  * Terms Of Use

Who is Redcats USA?  
  
Redcats USA, a member of the Redcats Home Shopping Division of the PPR® group, encompasses a group of home shopping brands that offer value-priced home goods, apparel from regular to extended sizes for women and men, and sporting goods. Redcats USA brands include such well-known names as Avenue® / Jessica London®, Woman Within® and Roaman's® for women’s extended size footwear and apparel sizes 12W & up; KingSize® offering men’s big & tall apparel from XL to 10XL, shoes to size 18EEEEEE; BrylaneHome®, offering home textile fashions and decorative accessories; BrylaneHome Kitchen®, your source for unusual and hard-to-find kitchen and home essentials, super-efficient gadgets, utensils, state-of-the-art cookware, cleaners, organizers, decorating accessories, bathroom fixer-uppers and much more. Our two outlet sites offer discounts up to 80%. Bargain Catalog Outlet™ and OneStopPlus™ offer a variety of women’s and men’s plus-size apparel and home fashions. Redcats USA’s brand portfolio also contains leading sporting goods divisions such as The Golf Warehouse™, The Sportsman’s Guide®, Bargain Outfitters® and Baseball Savings.com®. The Golf Warehouse offers golf equipment and accessories. The Sportsman’s Guide makes available value-priced outdoor gear and general merchandise. Bargain Outfitters offers top quality name brand gear, clothing and footwear. Baseball Savings.com offers baseball equipment, apparel, shoes, accessories and team logos. With this strong family of brands, many of which have been in existence for over 75 years, Redcats USA is one of the leading multi-channel retailers in the United States, and part of an international family of brands that make PPR a world leader in distribution to consumers and businesses. For Redcats USA brands' contact information click here.

Back To Top  
What Information Does Redcats USA Collect?   
  
  * Redcats USA collects information you provide to us about yourself to serve your needs. For example, if you place an order, or simply register on our site, you will provide to us your name, address, email address, phone number and credit card or other payment related information. When purchasing age-restricted products you will also be asked for your birth date. Of course, if you are placing an order, you will need to know the product(s) you wish to purchase. Whether you choose to provide us with this information is completely voluntary. If, however, you do not choose to provide such information you may not be able to purchase products from us or access certain services and/or portions of our websites.
  * Redcats USA also collects information you voluntarily submit when participating in one of our various services, promotions, programs or surveys. From your transactions and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.
  * Redcats USA also receives information about you from other companies, including, but not limited to information on your creditworthiness for private label credit card offers and products you may be interested in purchasing.

Redcats USA is a highly ethical company and requires the highest standard of conduct from our employees and business partners. As members of the Direct Marketing Association (DMA), the largest association for consumers and businesses interested in direct marketing, we adhere to the Guidelines for Ethical Business Practice, Shopping and Consumer Rights and the DMA's Privacy Promise. Questions about compliance with the DMA's Privacy Promise should be directed to [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com).

Back To Top  
How Does Redcats USA Use the Information Collected?  
  
Redcats USA uses the information collected as follows:

  * to process and complete your purchase transactions and provide the services you request;
  * to send you catalogs and other offerings to you via the mail;
  * to contact you about the status of your orders;
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you;
  * to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased;
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall customer shopping experience; and
  * for third-party advertising as described below click here.

Back To Top  
What Information Is Shared And With Whom Is It Shared?   
  
  * **Redcats USA Family of Brands:** Redcats USA is a family of direct mail catalogers and e-tailers, including, Woman Within, Roaman’s, Avenue / Jessica London, KingSize, BrylaneHome, BrylaneHome Kitchen, The Golf Warehouse, The Sportsman’s Guide and the outlet brands: Bargain Catalog Outlet and One Stop Plus. The parent of Redcats USA Family of companies is the French entity PPR. Individual Redcats USA brands share collected information (for example, postal addresses and telephone numbers) within the Redcats USA family and other entities within the PPR group of companies. Your email address is not shared within Redcats USA family of brands or the PPR group of companies.
  * **Third-Party Offers:** Redcats USA provides information (for example, postal addresses and telephone numbers) to certain outside companies and marketing partners so they can let our customers know about products or services that might be of interest to you. Your email address is not shared with such entities.
  * **Third-Party Advertising:** see below Click Here
  * **Legal Disclosures:** if Redcats USA is required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, in response to law enforcement inquiry or in compliance with applicable laws, Redcats USA will make such disclosure. Redcats USA also reserves the right to share information with legal authorities and other companies for purposes of fraud protection. In the event the ownership of all or a part of a business within the Redcats USA Family were to change, customer information pertinent to that business’s operations would likely be transferred to, or licensed for use by, the new owner.
  * **Redcats USA Credit Card Accounts:** we may share your information with the bank that issues Redcats USA division credit card accounts, World Financial Network National Bank. Shared information includes the date of the order, the type of payment, the amount of the order, whether there is any deferred billing and similar items.
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall customer shopping experience; and
  * for third-party advertising as described below click here.

If you do not want us to share your personal information within the Redcats USA family of brands, the PPR group of companies and third parties for promotional purposes, you may specify your preferences by [Clicking Here.](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com?body=PLEASE%20DO%20NOT%20SHARE%20MY%20PERSONAL%20INFORMATION%20WITH%20YOUR%20AFFILIATED%20ENTITIES%20OR%20THIRD%20PARTIES%20FOR%20MARKETING%20PURPOSES)

[ ](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com?body=PLEASE%20DO%20NOT%20SHARE%20MY%20PERSONAL%20INFORMATION%20WITH%20YOUR%20AFFILIATED%20ENTITIES%20OR%20THIRD%20PARTIES%20FOR%20MARKETING%20PURPOSES)Back To Top  
Does Redcats USA Use Third-Party Advertising?   
  
The Golf Warehouse uses a third-party advertising company to serve our ads across the Internet and sometimes on this site. This company collects anonymous (i.e., non-personally identifiable) information about your visits to our site and your interaction with our products and services in order to serve more relevant ads. These targeted advertisements may appear on our site or on other sites that you visit. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. If you do not want this company to collect this information, you may opt-out. Opt-ing out will not in any way affect your use of our site. To opt-out, [please click here](http://usucmweb.dotomi.com/2310/optout.html).

Back To Top  
How Can I Access and Correct Information Collected?  
  
You can update or correct your name, address, telephone number or email address anytime by visiting our websites and clicking on the My Account or Login link at the top of our websites and registering/logging in with your username/email address and password. You can also call, write, fax or email us to access or correct any of this information. See the table below to update your information with any or all of our brands.

| Brand | Edit Information Online | Postal Address | Customer Service Number | Fax Number  
---|---|---|---|---  
Avenue | Please visit My Account Section on www.avenue.com | Avenue / Jessica London  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 441-1362

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 978-8798

| (800) 448-5767  
Bargain Catalog Outlet | Please visit My Account Section on www.bcoutlet.com | BCO  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (888) 289-2815

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(888) 355-3096

| (888) 355-3098  
Bargain Outfitters | N/A | The Sportsman’s Guide, Inc.  
411 Farwell Avenue South  
St. Paul, MN 55075 | (888) 844-0667

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(888) 355-3096

| Not available  
BrylaneHome | Please visit My Account Section on www.brylanehome.com | BrylaneHome  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 677-0339

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 528-5149

| (800) 528-5152  
BrylaneHome | Please visit My Account Section on www.brylanehome.com | BrylaneHome  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 677-0339

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 528-5149

| (800) 528-5152  
BrylaneHome Kitchen | Please visit My Account on www.brylanehome.com | BrylaneHome Kitchen  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 784-8006

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 528-5149

| (800) 528-5152  
Jessica London | Please visit My Account on www.jessicalondon.com | Avenue / Jessica London  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 441-1362

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 978-8798

| (800) 448-5767  
KingSize | Please visit My Account on www.kingsizedirect.com | KingSize  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 677-0249

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 682-8095

| (800) 682-8109  
OneStopPlus | Please visit My Account on www.onestopplus.com | OneStopPlus  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 400-5527

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 456-7161

| (800) 456-9838  
Roaman's | Please visit My Account on www.roamans.com | Roaman's  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 677-0229

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 274-0260

| (800) 274-3102  
The Golf Warehouse & Baseball Savings.com | Please visit the Login section on www.tgw.com | The Golf Warehouse  
8851 East 34th St. North  
Wichita, KS 67226 | (888) 838-5551 | Not Available  
The Sportsman’s Guide | N/A | The Sportsman’s Guide, Inc.  
411 Farwell Ave. South  
St. Paul, MN 55075 | (888) 844-0667 | Not Available  
Woman Within | Please visit the My Account section on www.womanwithin.com | Woman Within  
PO Box 8320  
Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 | (800) 677-0216

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 456-7161

| (800) 456-9838  
  
**Any request to update your personal information may take up to 30 days for email requests and up to 60 days for mail and phone requests.**

Back To Top  
How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications from Redcats USA?  
  
_How to Be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List_

You can contact us by mail, phone or email at the relevant address or phone number listed on the above table for the specific brand from whom you wish to stop receiving paper catalogs. Please make sure to provide us with your exact name and address or the mailing label from your catalog so that we can identify you correctly.

We will make every effort to implement any choice you make as soon as possible, but you should allow approximately three months for mailing change requests to be fully implemented. Any mailings that you may receive during this time do not reflect your subscription status, and we ask that you please disregard them.

_How to Unsubscribe from an Email Marketing List_

To be removed from all of the email solicitation lists within the Redcats USA family of companies and to request that your information not be shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes, please [Click Here](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com?body=PLEASE%20DO%20NOT%20PLEASE%20DO%20NOT%20SEND%20ME%20ANY%20MARKETING%20MATERIALS,%20AND%20DO%20NOT%20SHARE%20MY%20PERSONAL%20INFORMATION%20WITH%20YOUR%20AFFILIATED%20ENTITIES%20OR%20THIRD%20PARTIES%20FOR%20MARKETING%20PURPOSES)

You will be removed from receiving future email solicitations, though you will still receive any email solicitations processed before this request was received. Please know that it may take up to 7 days to remove you from our emailing solicitation lists. If you choose to be removed from our emailing solicitation lists you will still continue to receive order and confirmation emails as well as emails relating to your other transactions. We will also no longer share your information with third parties for direct marketing purposes.

Back To Top  
Are Redcats USA Division Credit Cards Available?  
  
Yes. You can apply for a BrylaneHome (includes BrylaneHome Kitchen), Avenue / Jessica London, KingSize, Woman Within, Roaman’s and OneStopPlus, credit card account or Visa® Card account or a Sportsman’s Guide Visa Card account issued by World Financial Network National Bank to receive special offers and participate in exclusive brand benefits.

When you apply for one of these credit cards online, you provide your financial and personal information needed to process your application directly to World Financial Network National Bank. Redcats USA is independent of and not affiliated with World Financial Network National Bank.

To obtain a privacy policy, opt-out information, or contact information, for any Redcats USA private label credit card or Visa® Card accounts, you may contact the issuer of your card, the World Financial Network National Bank, by clicking through to the links provided below:

  * [Avenue](https://onlineaccess.mycreditcard.cc/avenue) / [Jessica London](https://onlineaccess.mycreditcard.cc/jessicalondon)

Back To Top  
Does Redcats USA Send Unsolicited Promotional Emails?   
  
No. Redcats USA only sends marketing email offers to customers who agree to receive them. Our online order form contains a pre-checked box signifying your consent to receive promotional emails. If you do not wish to receive such emails, please un-check the box.

If you are not placing an order and would like to request occasional promotional email offers, notifying you of special deals, web-only offers and product previews, you may sign up for Email Offers on this website, or call, fax or write us at the addresses listed above. Click Here

To remove your name from any email offer list, you may click the unsubscribe link in any of our marketing emails you receive, login to the Account Settings under the My Account or Login section of the website in question and email us that you want to unsubscribe, or contact the Customer Service Center for the specific brand. To remove you name from all our marketing emails, [Click Here](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com?body=DO%20NOT%20SEND%20ME%20ANY%20MARKETING%20MATERIALS,%20AND%20DO%20NOT%20SHARE%20MY%20PERSONAL%20INFORMATION%20WITH%20YOUR%20AFFILIATED%20ENTITIES%20OR%20THIRD%20PARTIES%20FOR%20MARKETING%20PURPOSES)

Registered website users who have purchased from one of our websites will receive standard order status communications, such as order confirmation, shipping dates, etc. via email at the registered email account the user has designated. Your choice to opt-in or opt-out of promotional emails will not affect the order status and registration service.

We may offer from time to time referral programs that permit you to submit information about other persons (each, a “Referred Person”), including, without limitation, email addresses, names, street addresses and other contact information so that they may receive information and/or promotional offers. We will use and store any such information that we collect from you about a Referred Person only to the extent necessary to carry out your request, and we will not use any such information for any other purpose unless the Referred Person consents to the use for such other purpose.

Back To Top  
How Does Redcats USA Safeguard the Information Collected?  
  
Redcats USA protects against unauthorized disclosures by limiting access only to those of our employees who need the information to do their jobs. Redcats USA employees are trained about their responsibility to protect our customers’ privacy. We limit the information we provide to outside companies to only the information we believe is appropriate to enable them to carry out their responsibilities under our contracts or to offer you products and services we think might be of interest to you. We contractually require that the information provided be used only for the specifically authorized purpose and that its confidentiality be maintained.

Back To Top  
How Secure Is My Online Transaction Secure?  
  
It is very secure. We use highly sophisticated technology to ensure that your shopping experience will be safe and secure. We encrypt your personal information, including your name, address, and credit card number when transmitting over the Internet using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) security software. We constantly update our security procedures and enhance our site to meet the very latest encryption standards. We retain a third party security firm to audit our procedures to ensure compliance with these standards. All of your sensitive information is scrambled before, during and after your order is placed on our site.

You may notice an unbroken key  or a closed lock  at the bottom of the page when you enter our "check-out" page. This means that your browser has opened a secure connection with our site! You can also check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."

**PLEASE NOTE THAT NORMAL EMAIL (SUCH AS USING CONTACT US OR YOUR HOME EMAIL) IS NOT ENCRYPTED AND THUS IS NOT A SECURE MEANS FOR TRANSMITTING CREDIT CARD INFORMATION OR ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU WISH TO KEEP PRIVATE AND SECURE.**

Back To Top  
Does Redcats USA Use Cookies?  
  
Yes. Redcats USA uses cookies to enhance the browsing and shopping experience on the Redcats USA family of brands’ websites. Cookies are small files or records that we place on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about your activities on the Redcats USA sites. There are absolutely no personally identifiable pieces of information stored anywhere in these files, and they are used solely by Redcats USA to enhance your shopping experience and to allow us to serve you better in the future. These cookies transmit information back to the computers at Redcats USA’s family of brands; these computers are, generally speaking, the only computers which are authorized to read such information. The information captured makes it possible for us (i) to speed navigation, keep track of items in your shopping cart, and provide you with custom tailored content; (ii) to remember information you gave to us so you don’t have to reenter it each time you visit the Redcats USA sites; (iii) to monitor the effectiveness of some of our marketing email campaigns; and (iv) to monitor total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of visitors served.

The Golf Warehouse uses Omniture and other service providers to help gather and analyze information about our customers (anonymous traffic, and from time to time, individual user activity) on our website. These service providers’ only role is to help us conduct our business and deliver the most relevant products and services. They are not permitted to use your personally indentifiable information for any secondary purpose.

Most people do not even know that cookies are being placed on their computers when they visit the Redcats USA family of brands’ sites or most other websites because web browsers are typically set to accept cookies. You can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you or you can turn off cookie acceptance altogether. However, if you refuse cookies, you will be unable to order from the Redcats USA sites using the Shopping Cart. You will still be able to browse our selection, but the order process requires that your Web Browser be set to allow cookies. Moreover, by not allowing cookies, your overall Internet browsing experience could be adversely affected.

Back To Top  
Does Redcats USA Aggregate Information?  
  
Yes. Redcats USA collects non-personal information about how users navigate through our websites. This statistical information is gathered in order to improve the Redcats USA sites. This information may be shared with Redcats USA affiliates or other outside companies. This aggregated statistical and navigational information does not include individual names, personal data or account information, so it does not identify you or any other customer.

Back To Top  
What is Redcats USA's Policy with Respect to Data Collection from Children?  
  
Redcats USA takes care to protect the privacy and safety of children. Our websites are not directed or targeted to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our websites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. If you are under the age of 13, you are welcome to browse our websites. However, you are not permitted to use any features of our site that require the collection of any personally identifiable information. If we learn that we have obtained personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will use reasonable efforts to immediately delete that data from our records.

Back To Top  
Whom Do I Contact If I Have Additional Questions or Concerns About This Policy?  
  
If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com).

Back To Top  
Links to Other Websites  
  
Redcats USA occasionally provides links on our websites to other non-affiliated websites to enhance your shopping experience. These other websites operate independently from Redcats USA and will have their own privacy and security policies. We strongly encourage you to review these policies at any website you visit. Redcats USA does not take responsibility for such non-affiliated websites.

Back To Top  
Effective Date and Policy Changes   
  
Redcats USA may from time to time make changes to its Privacy Policy to reflect changes in its privacy practices. Accordingly, Redcats USA reserves the right to revise or modify this Privacy Policy in whole or in part at any time. We will inform you of any update to our Privacy Policy by posting a notice on our website/s. The effective date of the updated policy will be the date posted on the notice. The updated policy shall replace any prior policies and will be applicable to all current and past users of our websites. This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 21st, 2010.

Back To Top
